#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/sumdenny (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Healthcare
Patient Advocacy
Acute Care

#### Certifications

Advanced Practice Registered Nurse Certified Nutrition Specialist

## Summer Denny, FNP

Family Nurse Practitioner at Arkansas Valley Regional Medical Center

Aurora, Colorado

## Summary

Quality-oriented recent college graduate with a Master of Science (M.S.) in Nursing (3.9 GPA), with 8 years of work experience. Aiming to leverage academic experience and a proven knowledge of continuity of care, outpatient care, and treatment planning to successfully fill the Nurse Practitioner role at your company. Frequently praised as hard-working by my peers, I can be relied upon to help your company achieve its goals.

## Experience

Arkansas Valley Regional Medical Center Family Nurse Practitioner June 2020 - Present (2 months) La Junta, Colorado, United States

Keystone Health and Wellness Center Nurse Practitioner September 2019 - Present (11 months) Greenwood Village, CO

Banner Health Travel NICU RN May 2019 - August 2019 (4 months) Phoenix, Arizona

Spring Valley Hospital Staff NICU RN October 2018 - May 2019 (8 months) Las Vegas, Nevada

Supplemental Health Care Travel NICU RN November 2017 - June 2018 (8 months)

# Fully Armored Family Health and Fitness Staff RN

July 2016 - November 2017 (1 year 5 months)

Carmel, IN

Carmel Total Fitness
Certified Personal Trainer/Nutrition Specialist
January 2016 - August 2016 (8 months)
Carmel, IN

I personally train clients in the gym setting. I track their workouts, weights, repetitions, encourage them and guide them towards proper nutrition.

St. Vincent Peyton Manning's Children's Hospital Neonatal/Pediatric Resource Float RN December 2013 - August 2016 (2 years 9 months)

Indianapolis, Indiana Area

I am pediatric resource nurse. I float to the general pediatric floors, pediatric emergency department, pediatric ICU, neonatal ICU, neonatal ICU step-down and continuing care nursery.

Assessed need for, ordered, obtained and interpreted appropriate lab tests.

Primary care, assessment and evaluation of neonatal patients.

Pharmacological and non-pharmacological management and treatment of various disorders and diseases.

Self-directed with astute judgment skills.

High level of personal accountability.

Effective counseling in health maintenance and disease management.

Managed care for post-operative patients through discharge.

Performed lab tests and communicated results.

Liaised between patients and physicians to ensure patient comprehension of treatment plans.

Instructed family members on proper discharge care.

Closely monitored acute conditions.

Demonstrated ability to lead and motivate outstanding healthcare teams.

Ensured HIPAA compliance.

Contributed substantially to successful department JCAHO accreditation.

Participated in unit-based Quality Assurance Program.

Followed infection control procedures.

Monitored fluid intake and output levels.

Scheduled patient admissions and discharges.

Supplemental Health Care

Travel NICU RN

August 2015 - November 2015 (4 months)

I was employed by Supplemental Healthcare and took a travel assignment at Riley in the NICU. I performed all the skills that I've listed in my previous experience at Riley.

Loving Care Agency, Inc

Pediatric Home Care RN

September 2013 - December 2013 (4 months)

I cared for a developmentally behind child. I performed g-tube feedings, worked on oral feedings, helped with developmental skills and administered medications. I attended school and therapies with the child.

Supplemental Health Care

Travel NICU RN

June 2013 - August 2013 (3 months)

Plantation General Hospital in Plantation, FL

I worked as a traveler in the neonatal ICU at Plantation General Hospital in Plantation, FL.

Assessed need for, ordered, obtained and interpreted appropriate lab tests.

Primary care, assessment and evaluation of neonatal patients.

Pharmacological and non-pharmacological management and treatment of various disorders and diseases.

Self-directed with astute judgment skills.

High level of personal accountability.

Effective counseling in health maintenance and disease management.

Managed care for post-operative patients through discharge.

Performed lab tests and communicated results.

Liaised between patients and physicians to ensure patient comprehension of treatment plans.

Instructed family members on proper discharge care.

Closely monitored acute conditions.

Demonstrated ability to lead and motivate outstanding healthcare teams.

Ensured HIPAA compliance.

Contributed substantially to successful department JCAHO accreditation.

Participated in unit-based Quality Assurance Program.

Followed infection control procedures.

Monitored fluid intake and output levels.

Scheduled patient admissions and discharges.

Riley Hospital for Children
Neonatal ICU Nurse
February 2012 - June 2013 (1 year 5 months)

Indianapolis, Indiana Area

Assessed need for, ordered, obtained and interpreted appropriate lab tests.

Primary care, assessment and evaluation of neonatal patients.

Pharmacological and non-pharmacological management and treatment of various disorders and diseases.

Self-directed with astute judgment skills.

High level of personal accountability.

Effective counseling in health maintenance and disease management.

Managed care for post-operative patients through discharge.

Performed lab tests and communicated results.

Liaised between patients and physicians to ensure patient comprehension of treatment plans.

Instructed family members on proper discharge care.

Closely monitored acute conditions.

Demonstrated ability to lead and motivate outstanding healthcare teams.

Ensured HIPAA compliance.

Contributed substantially to successful department JCAHO accreditation.

Participated in unit-based Quality Assurance Program.

Followed infection control procedures.

Monitored fluid intake and output levels.

Scheduled patient admissions and discharges.

### Education

The Ohio State University

Family Nurse Practitioner-MSN, Family Practice Nurse/Nursing (2016 - 2019)

Indiana University–Purdue University Indianapolis

Bachelor of Science (BS), Registered Nursing/Registered

Nurse · (2007 - 2011)